Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 92: Cornell student paper attacks stand on union, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 93: Cornell students have to pass picket lines going to class, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 94: Cornell U. strike off, AFL union recognized, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 95: Cornell Univ. rejects mediation board, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 96: Dewey asked to intervene in Cornell strike, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 97: Labor relations students appeal, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 98: Maintenance workers begin Cornell strike, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 99: NLRB to get hearing data, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 100: Set up grievance plan in walkout at Cornell, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Item 101: Students urge probe into Cornell strike, 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 9)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Newspapers to be photocopied and noted, Publication (Box 118, Folder 10)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Is this your story?, 1968; Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: How safe is your jobunder Civil Service?, 1968; Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Will payday solve your problems?, 1968; Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Winning new benefits for members through welfare plans, 1954; Publication (Box 118, Folder 11)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Fiftieth Anniversary Souvenir History of the New York Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1914-1964, Publication (Box 118, Folder 12)
    Notes: Souvenir book
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Newspapers articles that need photocopying, if used., 1950; Publication (Box 118, Folder 13)
    Notes: All articles are about the Maintenance workers strike at Cornell, and duplicate some of the articles already photocopied. They have been placed in a mylar sleeve for safe keeping.
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Dollar$ & $ense, the SEIU Consumer Newsletter, 1965-1968 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1968 - (Summer, Mar., Jan.); 1967 - (Nov., Sept., June, Mar., Jan.); 1966 - (Nov., Sept., May, Apr.); 1965 - (Nov.)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Background of 1950 Strike - report, Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Building Service, 14th Anniversary, Local 32B, April 1948, Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Going up!: the story of Local 32B, 1955; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Helping its own, Local 32B's retraining program holds promise for workers, 1963; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
    Notes: Industrial Bulletin, Oct. 1963
  - Item 5: Report of Executive Officers of Local 32B, 1959; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Special Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
    Notes: Issued by Local 32B. May 18, 1950. 2 copies
  - Item 7: Special Notice to All Tenants in Office Buildings from Building Service Employees International Union, Local 32-J, Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
    Author: Building Service Employees International Union, Local 32-J
  - Item 8: The Local 32B Health Center, 1960; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The Washington Post, 1966; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
    Notes: Sunday, July 3, 1966. 2 copies
  - Item 10: This is your union, 1960; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: 32B wins fight for recognition and city-wide fair wage scale, 1960; Publication (Box 119, Folder 2)
- Registered Nurses Guild, Publication (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: News of the Registered Nurses Guild No. 312, 1948-1954 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    Author: Registered Nurses Guild No. 312
    Notes: Many issues, some dated, some not - if used heavily, needs preservation copying
  - Item 2: The Bulletin [newsletter from Registered Nurses Guild No. 312] - many issues of both, some dated, some not - if used heavily, needs preservation copying, 1948-1954 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    Notes: Newsletter from Registered Nurses Guild No. 312. Many issues, some dated, some not - if used heavily, needs preservation copying
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Requirements and benefits of Civil Service Employment in the Department of Public Health of the City of San Francisco, Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Author: Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250
  - Item 2: Hospital and Institutional Workers' Union, Local 250, 1948-1953 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Report to Locals, BSEIU, 1948-1953 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.3, no.12
  - Item 4: AFL to the Building Service Workers of Syracuse, NY, Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: An important message from the Hospital & Institutional Workers Union, Local 250.., Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Around the Clock, 1953; Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Author: Building Service Employees International Union
    Notes: Published by Local No. 29 (May 1953)
  - Item 7: BSEIU, AFL-CIO Insurance Program, 1964; Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Author: Building Service Employees of Central New York Welfare Fund
  - Item 8: Group Life, Hospital and Surgical Insurance., 1964; Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Author: Hudson Valley Building Service Employees' Welfare Fund
  - Item 9: Information and instructions to the members of Chicago Flat Janitors Union, Local No.1, 1940; Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Author: Building Service Employees' International Union
  - Item 10: Keeping the records straight, 1959; Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Local 164 News, published by BSEIU, 1948-1953 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.6, no.11
  - Item 12: Local 372, Sales and Service Union, BSEIU, AFL-CIO, 1948-1953 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Report of Executive Officers of Local 32B, 1959; Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Report on labor dispute at Cornell Univ., 1950; Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Report on the strike of the Building Service Employees International Union, Publication (Box 119, Folder 4)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: BSEIU Local officers, Quarterly, 1958-1960 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    Author: BSEIU
    Notes: no.5-6, 9-10,12- 17
  - Item 2: Welfare and Pension Plans, Publication (Box 119, Folder 5)
    Notes: no. 1,3-5, 7
- Registered Nurses Guild, Publication (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Do you know there is a union for registered professional nurses?, 1954; Publication (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: News of the Registered Nurses Guild No. 312 & The Bulletin [, Publication (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Bulletin, Publication (Box 119, Folder 6)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Union citizen is a better citizen, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Announcing the Charles Hardy Memorial Scholarship awards, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Building Operation and Janitorial Service Institute, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Know your own International death benefit gratuity!, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Too old to work at 40?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Ty kontra Twemu Majstrowi, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Union League-Union buster, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Wear your union insignia, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: What union contract means to hospital workers, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: When hunting for the facts, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: A Union citizen is a better citizen, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Automation and the public employee, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Boston Building Service, 1952; Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. III, no. 1 (March, 1952)
  - Item 14: Building Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, Repeal 14(b)!, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Building Service Employees International Union, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Officers' Report. 12th General Convention, Building Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1960; Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Officers' Report. 14th General Convention, Building Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1968; Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Service Workers' manual, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: We are B.S.E.I.U. and we're going places!, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: What's funny about public employment?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Why join a Union ?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Your Social Security means cash to you, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Your union: a two-pronged drive for equality, security, and justice, Publication (Box 120, Folder 1)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Death benefit claim and Officers' certificate, Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Hospital workers: are you working for peanuts?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Labor-Management Reporting and disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: New honor announced for BSEIU's McFetridge, 1960; Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Newspaper articles from the Daily Tribune - clipped together, too many to list, 1961; Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: This is a report of certain events concerning the employee strike., Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
    Notes: This information was obtained by a group of students who attended a union meeting on Tuesday evening the 28th of November, interviewed union officials and inspected available affidavits bearing on the strike.
  - Item 7: Twelfth General Convention Committees, Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Union Internacional de Personal de Servicio de Edificios, Publication (Box 120, Folder 2)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Down with unions!, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Fashions change..., Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Here's an idea...for you!, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Shhhh, Somebody's sleeping here!, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: What you will gain from membership in the Building Service Union, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Which way is the wind blowing?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Czy Mozesz Liczyc na Poparcie w Celu Uzyskania Rezultatow?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Put this in your pipe.., Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Spreading the good word about unionismthrough print, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
    Notes: Conference packet. 2 copies
  - Item 10: Welcome!, Publication (Box 120, Folder 3)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 2 Prosecutors spur track crime inquiry, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: DA seeks $360,000 paid DeKoning Union by builders, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Governor's statement on inquiry, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor experts got $164,000 at track, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Labor leader grabs welfare funds of union, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Labor pacifiers got $164,000..., 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Licensing of raceway workers ordered after racket testimony, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Local 32-E paid $63,000 yearly in fees to Lewis Insurance Agency for 'service', 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: McKeown wants to debate Sprague, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Moreland Raceway inquiry begun as lent and DeKoning are heard, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Mushrooming of Trot races spawns scandals across US, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Ownership of 7 tracks to be studied - DeKoning arrested in Nassau, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Raceway figure is identified as fugitive in 1925 murders, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Raceway hearing opens here today, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Raceway inquiry bares testimony, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Raceway inquiry in Nassau widened, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Raceway to submit no more testimony, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Raceway workers must be licensed, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Raceways board asks replacement by new Commissioner, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Racketeers tied to track purchase, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Subpoenas to seek track ownerships, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Union welfare funds, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Wicks paid visits to Fay in Sing Sing, Dewey asks why, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Yonkers job forms rejected by State, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Insurance inquiry into funds of 32-E ordered by Dewey, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Nassau judge admits he is accused of sharing track program profits, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: Say McKeown Ducks tie with DeK in '50 campaign, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Wagner loses Mr. X case, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Yonkers raceway closed by Dewey in labor scandal, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: Yonkers track ban is lifted, 1953; Publication (Box 120, Folder 4)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report to Locals Newsletter, 1958-1960 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb. 1958; Jan., Mar.- May, July, Sept., Nov. 1960; Jan.-Feb., Apr., June 1961; Aug., Sept., Nov. 1959
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: BSEIU Local Unions in action: 1945-1950, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Highlights of the Social Security Act, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: Printed copy
  - Item 3: Our own "Rupe von Wankle" wakes up to see, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: RTL Newsletter, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1955 September 20
  - Item 5: Test your Local's IQ, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The ABC's of wage stabilization, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The needs of Public Employees, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: This is your union: BSEIU, 1957; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Wage rates and ranges for selected occupations in public buildings, parks, hospitals, and schools 1956, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: For you and your family, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: I like working in a hospital but, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Stop accidents before they happen!, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: The union contract, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: What it costs not to belong to a union, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: When hunting for the facts, Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Aids to organizers, 1957; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Automation and unemployment in the Service Industries, 1961; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Building Service Employees International Union - 1. What it is 2.How it works 3.How it can help you, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Do you support higher education?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Money isn't everything, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: PO CO Wstepowac do Unii?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Sie und IHR arbeitgeber, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: USTED vs. El Patron, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Warum einer gewerkschaft beitreten?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: What it costs NOT to belong to a union, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: You vs. your boss, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: City and County hospitals, Wage rate survey for selected occupations, 1964; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: General Economic Trends [Chicago, 1955-59], 1955-1959 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: In the matter of the Arbitration pursuant to Section 22 of the Sloan Agreement between Local 32-B, Building Service Employees' International Union and Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Inc., 1939; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Marina City a new dimension in urban living, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Porque Asociarse a una union?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: State Hospital wage range survey for selected occupations, 1960; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Trends in State and Local Government, 1955-1959 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Wage rates and ranges for selected occupations in Cities and Other Governmental Units, 1958; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Wage rates and ranges for selected occupations in Cities and Other Governmental Units, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Wage rates and ranges for selected occupations in Cities and Other Governmental Units, 1960; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Wage rates and ranges for selected occupations in Cities and Public Schools, 1963; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: When hunting for the facts, Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: BSEIU this is your union, Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Do you need a union?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Is this your story?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Who says hospital workers need unions?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Brief talks about welfare and pension plans, 1959-1961 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Economic trends in selected Service Industries, 1955-1959 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: General Economic Trends [United States 1955-59], 1955-1959 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Keeping the records straight, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Keeping the records straight, 1959; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Report to locals Newsletter, 1961; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: April 11, 1961 issue
  - Item 11: Too old to work at 40? Too old to work at 35?, Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Wage rates and ranges for selected occupations in Cities and Public Schools, 1961; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Wage rates and ranges for selected occupations in Cities and Public Schools, 1962; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: When hunting for the facts, Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Resolutions (12th General Convention) - Annual, 1960; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
- BSEIU (Building Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How to organize local building trades councils, Publication (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: To avoid strikes and lock-outs, Publication (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Button Workers' Protective Union, Publication (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report on the industrial situation at Muscatine, Iowa, 1912; Publication (Box 121, Folder 7)
    Author: Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America. Commission on the Church and Social Service.
  - Item 2: Report on the industrial situation at Muscatine, Iowa, 1912; Publication (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The labor war of Muscatine, Iowa: being a story of the Strike of the Button Workers, Publication (Box 121, Folder 7)
    Author: Oliver C. Wilson
- California Labor School, Publication (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: California Labor School; California negotiated clauses for Occupational Health and Safety, 1946; Publication (Box 121, Folder 8)
    Notes: Course handbook
  - Item 2: California Labor School; California negotiated clauses for Occupational Health and Safety, 1976; Publication (Box 121, Folder 8)
- CSEA (California State Employees Association), Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1964; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Author: California State Employees Assoc.
  - Item 2: Annual Report, 1965; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Annual Report, 1967; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
- CSEA (California State Employees Association), Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: CSEA Handbook, 1962; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: First study report on formal systems of representation for California public employees, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Author: California State Employees' Association. Research Section
  - Item 3: Why doesn't someone tell me these things?; Measure CSEA's value to you, Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
- Alberta Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Annual submission to the Legislature, 1962; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Author: Alberta Federation of Labour, C.L.C.
  - Item 2: Annual submission to the Legislature, 1965; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Memorandum of Legislative Programme, 1948; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
- Alberta Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Annual submission to the Legislature, 1963; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Annual submission to the Legislature, 1964; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Principals and policy of the Alberta Federation of Labor based upon its affiliation with the trades and labor congress of Canada from which it was duly chartered in the year 1912, Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Re: Questionnaires, circulated among affiliates, Alberta Federation of Labour, 1963; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Report: Labor management hearingEdmonton, Alberta, 1963; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Report presented to the Sixth convention of the Alberta Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 1961; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
- Alberta Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Addendum to the submission to the Special Committee on Workmen's Compensation, 1964; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Bill 89 - A bill respecting Public Works, 1965; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Board of Industrial Relations Order No. 1, 2, 19, 22, 1965; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Brief of argument presented by Alberta Federation of Labour, C.L.C., 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, 1963-1964 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.1, 3